Time to own up.
是时候坦白了。
When you‘re sitting at your computer, do you work solidly all day?
当你坐在电脑前时，你是一整天都在踏踏实实地工作吗？
Or do you allow yourself to become distracted now and again... to open a few extra tabs, check social media, read a spot of news, browse the latest fashion trends, maybe catch up on some celebrity gossip, and look at some...
还是会时不时地让自己分心......打开几个额外的标签页，查看社交媒体，读一点新闻，浏览最新的时尚潮流，也许还会了解一些名人八卦，或者看看其他的......
Stop!
停！
You’re ’cyberloafing‘.
你这是在“网络摸鱼”。
The unwieldy word is a combination of ’cyber‘, which means ’related to computers‘, and ’loafing‘, which means ’relaxing in a lazy way‘.
这个拗口的词是由“cyber”（意思是“与计算机有关的”）和“loafing”（意思是“以懒散的方式放松”）组合而成的。
We do it, and we do it a lot.
我们会这么做，而且还经常这么做。
A study from the University of Texas suggests we are guilty of this form of procrastination for 14% of our working day.
德克萨斯大学的一项研究表明，在我们的工作日中，有14%的时间都在犯这种拖延的毛病。
On a Friday afternoon, I expect it’s more than that.
我猜在周五下午，这个比例会更高。
I‘ll admit to indulging in the odd bout of cyberloafing myself.
我承认自己也会偶尔沉迷于网络摸鱼。
In fact I’ve already done it in the course of writing this story.
事实上，在写这篇文章的过程中我就已经这么做了。
OK, more than once.
好吧，不止一次。
But it‘s a slippery slope.
但这是一个滑坡效应。
It can damage your productivity and even your career.
它会损害你的工作效率，甚至影响你的职业生涯。
Because according to the Univeristy of Texas research, each time a worker gets sidetracked by the internet it takes an average of 23 minutes to get back to work.
因为根据德克萨斯大学的研究，每次员工被网络转移注意力后，平均需要23分钟才能重新回到工作状态。
More than that, cyberloafing has a dark side, according to a report published in The Journal of Psychosocial Research on Cyberspace.
不仅如此，根据发表在《网络空间心理社会研究杂志》上的一份报告，网络摸鱼还有其阴暗面。
It argues that cyberloafing is connected to several negative personality traits.
报告指出，网络摸鱼与一些负面的人格特质有关。
People who cyberloaf are more likely to be manipulative, self-interested and narcissistic.
网络摸鱼的人更有可能具有操控欲、自私自利和自恋的特点。
Furthermore, people with these traits are less likely to feel remorse about avoiding work, and less concerned about getting caught.
此外，具有这些特质的人不太可能对逃避工作感到懊悔，也不太担心被发现。
Why do we do it?
我们为什么会这么做呢？
For some, it’s undoubtedly an escape from the drudgery of what they‘re supposed to be doing.
对一些人来说，这无疑是一种逃避他们本该做的枯燥乏味工作的方式。
Or a way of avoiding tackling that ever growing in-tray.
或者是一种避免处理那不断增多的待办事项的方法。
Some might get a feeling of satisfaction, get a buzz from finding a great deal online.
有些人可能会从中获得满足感，从在网上找到大优惠中得到兴奋感。
But overall, it’s something that takes you away from what you‘re actually being paid to do, or paying to do: if you’re a student.
但总的来说，这会让你偏离你实际上被付钱去做，或者你花钱去做的事情，如果你是学生的话。
When you have the whole world of the internet at your fingertips, it‘s hard to resist.
当整个互联网世界触手可及时，这很难抗拒。
How do we nip it in the bud?
我们要如何防患于未然呢？
If you can truly ask yourself why you are cyberloafing, then that can help identify the base problem.
如果你能真正问问自己为什么会网络摸鱼，那么这有助于找出根本问题。
And if that sounds like too much hard work, you could just switch off the internet for a couple of hours!
如果这听起来太费劲，你可以直接关掉网络几个小时！
So in the meantime, let me just close those extra tabs...
所以，在此期间，让我先关掉那些额外的标签页......